<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on ito | Track infections, not people</title><link>/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on ito | Track infections, not people</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TCN Coalition</title><link>/blog/tcn-coalition-founding/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 01:00:40 +0600</pubDate><guid>/blog/tcn-coalition-founding/</guid><description>On Sunday, April 5, 2020, a global, open coalition emerged for digital contact tracing protocols to flatten the curve and stop the spread of COVID-19 while reopening the economy. We at ITO are proud to be one of the founding teams, after our successful participation in the #WirVsVirus Hackathon.
Over the course of the past few weeks, the global community of technologists, privacy experts, and epidemiologists have worked tirelessly towards a secure, privacy-first, GDPR-compliant and open-source approach to enable globally compatible contact tracing.</description></item><item><title>What we think about PEPP-PT</title><link>/blog/statement-what-we-think-about-pepp-pt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 12:29:40 +0600</pubDate><guid>/blog/statement-what-we-think-about-pepp-pt/</guid><description>In order to understand our situation, we would first like to briefly describe how things evolved from our perspective.
We were not very surprised when the project PEPP-PT [Pan-European Privacy-Preserving Proximity Tracing] publicly launched, since it had been announced that some relevant institutions were working on a solution during the #WeVsVirus results ceremony. While we understand that it was unforeseeable how much progress the hackathon teams would make towards a tracing solution in one weekend, we did assume that once it became clear how many highly qualified developers, data protection officers and other experts were involved, a common discourse would emerge.</description></item></channel></rss>